http://www.ctp.at/data-privacy-statement

Data privacy statement
CTP values your right to privacy highly and the protection of your personal data is of particular concern to us. We process your data exclusively in accordance with the legal regulations (GDPR, telecommunications act). If the processing of personal data is necessary, the processing is based on Article 6 (1) lit.b GDPR.
Collection and storage of personal data
If you contact us by means of the CTA (call-to-action) element on our website, send us a job-application or an e-mail, your data provided will be processed by us in order to deal with your request and for follow-up questions. We do not transfer your data to any third parties without your approval.
Security
We have taken several security measures to protect personal information. Our databases are protected by technical and organizational measures that restrict access to any kind of information to specially authoritzed persons.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device by means of the browser. Cookies are used to enhance your visit to our website. Some of the cookies remain on your device and enable us to recognise your browser the next time you visit, unless you delete them.
You can adjust your browser’s settings to get information when cookies are used, in order that you can decide whether to accept them or not in certain cases. The functions of our website may be limited if you do not accept cookies.
Website analysis
Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service from Google Inc. (www.google.de). For this purpose cookies are used which enable an analysis of the use of the website by its users. Information generated in this way is transferred to the provider's server and stored there. You can prevent cookies from being stored by making the relevant settings in your browser software.
Your rights
You have the right to information about the data that we have saved concerning your identity and, if necessary, the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. If you have any questions about collection, processing or use of your personal data or for information, correction, blocking or deletion of data, as well as withdrawal of consent or objection to certain use of data, please contact us directly, using the contact details provided on our website information page (Disclosure).
CTP
Contact
History
Quality
Sustainability
Vision and Mission
News
SOLUTIONS
Nitrous oxide (laughing gas)
